Guide to the Dr. Huey P. Newton Foundation Inc. Collection
Department of Special Collections
- Series 1: Huey P. Newton Papers, 1
  - Subseries 6: Speeches/Lectures/Interviews, 6
    - Speaking Engagements 1977 - 1978 (Box 57, Folder 2)
      Stanford Organizing Committee "Disorientation Week" activities - April 1978
    - Speaking Engagements Unable to Make 1970 - 1972 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Servant: Interview Request1977 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Signed Contracts Not Executed1970 - 1976 (Box 57, Folder 5)
      some Stronghold contracts
    - Bauer - Newton Interviews Article1970 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Huey Newton Speaks1970 (Box 57, Folder 7)
      a published interview by Mark Lane in the California State Prison, July 4th
    - The Whole World Revolution Will Be Kicked Off...Interview with H.P.N.1970 (Box 57, Folder 8)
      transcript of interview with "LNS", New Haven, Conn., Aug. 21st
    - Interview with Huey P. Newton, by Mark Lane [1 of 2]1970 (Box 57, Folder 9)
      transcript of interview, Sept. 17th
    - Interview with Huey P. Newton, by Mark Lane [2 of 2]1970 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Huey's Message at Boston College November 18, 19701970 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - H.P.N. at New York Community College - November 19, 19701970 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - [Recorded conversations with Huey Newton, by Kai T. Erikson][1 of 2]1971 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - [Recorded conversations with Huey Newton, by Kai T. Erikson][2 of 2]1971 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Newton-Ericson Transcripts [1 of 2]1971 (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Newton-Ericson Transcripts [2 of 2]1971 (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - Yale Press Conference - Feb 2, 1971 [1 of 3]1971 (Box 58, Folder 1)
      transcript of press conference with Erik Erickson, Yale University Press people and people from Trumbull College
    - Yale Press Conference - Feb 2, 1971 [2 of 3]1971 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Yale Press Conference - Feb 2, 1971 [3 of 3]1971 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - [For Gwen Hodges: Part I of the book: 'Explorations: A Dialogue Between Erik Erikson and Huey P. Newton"1971 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Press Statement from Huey P. Newton on George Jackson1971 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Georgia State College - Huey P. Newton, Speaks1972 (Box 58, Folder 6)
      copy of speech
    - West Magazine Interview with Huey P. Newton by Digby Diehl L.A. Times [1 of 2]1972 (Box 58, Folder 7)
      manuscript of interview
    - West Magazine Interview with Huey P. Newton by Digby Diehl L.A. Times [2 of 2]1972 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Newton - Lockwood - Playboy Article1972 (Box 58, Folder 9)
      letter regarding the status of the interview
    - Playboy Interview: HPN (Box 58, Folder 10)
      actual magazine article
    - Of Panthers in Prisons: An Interview with Huey P. Newton by Fred Hiestand & Jim Smith1972 (Box 58, Folder 11)
      for "The National Lawyers Guild Practitioner" draft of interview plus copy of serial {vol. 29, nos 3-4, summer 1972)
    - Interview with Huey, Franz Schurmann and Alberto Martinelli, Italy1972 (Box 58, Folder 12)
      transcript from taped interview Sept 30th
    - Victory Statement (5-15-73) 1973 (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Interviews - 19771977 - 1979 (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Editorials 1977 (Box 58, Folder 15)
      television editorial "Huey is Back" plus Huey's rebuttal
    - T.V. Shows1973 - 1978 (Box 58, Folder 16)
      transcript of "Firing Line" with William F. Buckley plus letters scheduling TV interviews
    - Statements by HPN 1974, 1978, 1980 (Box 58, Folder 17)
      during trial plus statement about his mid east tour.
    - HPN Releases (Box 58, Folder 18)
      Printed pamphlet "The State vs. Huey P. Newton" done in 1979 plus bios about Huey
    - Penthouse Interview w/ Huey P. Newton 3/801980 (Box 59, Folder 1)
      photocopy of interview
    - Statement by HPN to Judge Karesh 5/28/811981 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Huey Newton Speaks to the Movement (Box 59, Folder 3)
      printed pamphlet "Huey Newton Speaks to "The Movement" and the Ten Point Program of The Black Panther Party" reprinted without permission by Tuesday the Ninth Committee and The Berkely Commune
    - Merritt Lecture Series H.P.N. [1 of 2]1972 (Box 59, Folder 4)
      drafts of lectures
    - Merritt Lecture Series H.P.N. [2 of 2]1972 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Intercommunal Youth Institute Goals/Notes (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - HPN on the SLA (Box 59, Folder 7)
      printed question to HPN and his response
    - Patricia Pomerantz, Artist Management1977 - 1979 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Press Statement by Huey P. Newton, Servant of the People Upon Return to USA From the People's Republic of China1970 (Box 59, Folder 9)
- Series 2: Black Panther Party Records, 2
  - Subseries 1: Correspondence, 1
    - BPP Correspondence to: Amnesty International 9-4-801980 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Black Congressional Caucus 1972 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      list of memebers of the Black Congressional Caucus plus letter from Ron Dellums
    - Black Student Alliance - Correspondence to/from 1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      from Duke University, Durham, N.C.
    - Chicago - Peoples Law Office - Correspondence 19781978 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Emory Douglas1971 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      includes paper "Libreria Popolare" from Italy
    - Correspondence re: Expulsion of June & David Hilliard1974 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Tony Kline, Esq.1972 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Oakland Small Business Development Center - Jobs for Parolees1972 - 1973 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Larry Pinkney [San Francisco Black Caucus]1972 - 1974 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Police Dept. Info.1977 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Project Committee (1 May 69) #21969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      letters from the U.S. Committee to Aid the National Liberation Front of South Vietnam
    - Public Advocates Correspondence [Fred Hiestand] [1 of 2]1972 - 1973 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Public Advocates Correspondence [Fred Hiestand] [2 of 2]1972 - 1973 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Servant: Correspondence (Outgoing) (Since 7/3/77)1977 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Servant Correspondence [1 of 2]1970 - 1974 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Servant Correspondence [2 of 2]1970 - 1974 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Phillip Shapiro, M.D.1973 - 1974 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Letter to Fay Stender1973 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - [Letter]1972 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Letters to Be Written1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - General Requests for Material and/or Specific Information [1 of 13]1971 - 1973 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - General Requests for Material and/or Specific Information [2 of 13]1971 - 1973 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - General Requests for Material and/or Specific Information [3 of 13]1971 - 1973 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - General Requests for Material and/or Specific Information [4 of 13]1971 - 1973 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - General Requests for Material and/or Specific Information [5 of 13]1971 - 1973 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - General Requests for Material and/or Specific Information [6 of 13]1971 - 1973 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - General Requests for Material and/or Specific Information [7 of 13]1971 - 1973 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - General Requests for Material and/or Specific Information [8 of 13]1971 - 1973 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - General Requests for Material and/or Specific Information [9 of 13]1971 - 1973 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - General Requests for Material and/or Specific Information [10 of 13]1971 - 1973 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - General Requests for Material and/or Specific Information [11 of 13]1971 - 1973 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - General Requests for Material and/or Specific Information [12 of 13]1971 - 1973 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - General Requests for Material and/or Specific Information [13 of 13]1971 - 1973 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Letters Requesting Information [1 of 4]1970 - 1973 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Letters Requesting Information [2 of 4]1970 - 1973 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Letters Requesting Information [3 of 4]1970 - 1973 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Letters Requesting Information [4 of 4]1970 - 1973 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Standard Support Letters Sent Out [1 of 7]1970 - 1972 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Standard Support Letters Sent Out [2 of 7]1970 - 1972 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Standard Support Letters Sent Out [3 of 7]1970 - 1972 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Standard Support Letters Sent Out [4 of 7]1970 - 1972 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Standard Support Letters Sent Out [5 of 7]1970 - 1972 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Standard Support Letters Sent Out [6 of 7]1970 - 1972 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Standard Support Letters Sent Out [7 of 7]1970 - 1972 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Subseries 2: Internal Documents, 2
    - Central Committee Info. [1 of 4]1969 - 1974 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Central Committee Info. [2 of 4]1969 - 1974 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Central Committee Info. [3 of 4]1969 - 1974 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Central Committee Info. [4 of 4]1969 - 1974 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Central Body Meetings1977 - 1979 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Central Headquarters Phone Messages1977 - 1979 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Misc - Phone Numbers, etc.[1994 / 1995] (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Property Maintenance File---Glen Godfrey (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Innerparty Memorandums1972 - 1974 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Inner Party Memorandums 1979 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - [Direction of the Party, by JoNina]1980 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Original Writing of the B.P.P.'s What We Want What We Believe (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Directives (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Directives1971 - 1974 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Legal Manifesto Effective 1-11-71 Top Secret1971 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Anti-Imperialist Delegation 1970 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - General Reports1980 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Reports on Comrades1977 - 1979 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Public Relations Weekly Reports1972 - 1973 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Communications Sheets [1 of 6]1971 - 1973 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Communications Sheets [2 of 6]1971 - 1973 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Communications Sheets [3 of 6]1971 - 1973 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Communications Sheets [4 of 6]1971 - 1973 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Communications Sheets [5 of 6]1971 - 1973 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Communications Sheets [6 of 6]1971 - 1973 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Weekly Cadre Reports1977 - 1978 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Section Progress Reports [1 of 10]1972 - 1974 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Section Progress Reports [2 of 10]1972 - 1974 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Section Progress Reports [3 of 10]1972 - 1974 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Section Progress Reports [4 of 10]1972 - 1974 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Section Progress Reports [5 of 10]1972 - 1974 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Section Progress Reports [6 of 10]1972 - 1974 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Section Progress Reports [7 of 10]1972 - 1974 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Section Progress Reports [8 of 10]1972 - 1974 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Section Progress Reports [9 of 10]1972 - 1974 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Section Progress Reports [10 of 10]1972 - 1974 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Requests to Start B.P.P. Centers1971 - 1972 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Black Panther Party Southern Calif. Chapter 1977 - 1978 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - General Reports From Chapters & Branches (weekly)1972 - 1973 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - [San Quentin Cadre B.P.P.]1971 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - New Haven & Misc. Info. 12/9/941970; 1994 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Intercommunal Contacts [1 of 3]1969 - 1973 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      ALS: to Bobby and Huey, [ca. 1971 Sept. 24] / Jean Genet.;Attica: USA / Jean Genet. AMss, 3 p.;Attica: USA / Jean Genet. TMs, 6 p.
    - Intercommunal Contacts [2 of 3]1969 - 1973 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Intercommunal Contacts [3 of 3]1969 - 1973 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - [Lists and contacts] [1 of 2] (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - [Lists and contacts] [2 of 2] (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Contacts - 1977 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Contributors1973 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Consolidated Application Info./ State Department of Education Comprehensive Program Planning [Wilson Donation List ] [1 of 6] (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Consolidated Application Info./ State Department of Education Comprehensive Program Planning [Wilson Donation List ] [2 of 6] (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Consolidated Application Info./ State Department of Education Comprehensive Program Planning [Wilson Donation List ] [3 of 6] (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Consolidated Application Info./ State Department of Education Comprehensive Program Planning [Wilson Donation List ] [4 of 6] (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Consolidated Application Info./ State Department of Education Comprehensive Program Planning [Wilson Donation List ] [5 of 6] (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Consolidated Application Info./ State Department of Education Comprehensive Program Planning [Wilson Donation List ] [6 of 6] (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Mailing Lists Before 1976 [1 of 4] (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Mailing Lists Before 1976 [2 of 4] (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Mailing Lists Before 1976 [3 of 4] (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Mailing Lists Before 1976 [4 of 4] (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Mailing Lists: After Jan. 19761976 - 1977 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Weekly Reports [Mailing lists] [1 of 6]1976 - 1977 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Weekly Reports [Mailing lists] [2 of 6]1976 - 1977 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Weekly Reports [Mailing lists] [3 of 6]1976 - 1977 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Weekly Reports [Mailing lists] [4 of 6]1976 - 1977 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Weekly Reports [Mailing lists] [5 of 6]1976 - 1977 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Weekly Reports [Mailing lists] [6 of 6]1976 - 1977 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Mailing Lists 1976 - 1977 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Mailing Lists 1976 - 1977 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - List of Affiants (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Lloyd A Barbee, State Representative-- Wisonsin Legis. [1 of 2]1971 - 1974 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Lloyd A Barbee, State Representative-- Wisonsin Legis. [2 of 2]1971 - 1974 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Joe Barrington1970 - 1974 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Shirley Chisholm1972 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Ronald V. Dellums1977 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Mary I. Dougherty (Molly) (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - David G. DuBois1972 - 1973 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - David Horowitz1971 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - [Hunter, Lowell]1979; 1989 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - [Fredrika Newton - Deed of Trust / Crime Report from 1968] (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Fay Stender1970 - 1971 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - B.C.D.C. [Berkeley Community Development Council] Board of Directors Election1972 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - N.A.A.C.P.1977 - 1978 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Peoples Temple (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - The S.L.A.1973 - 1974 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Black Panther Party - Offers to Help, Contributions, etc. - 19691968 - 1970 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Cable TV [1 of 2]1972 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Cable TV [2 of 2]1972 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Cal-Pac [1 of 2]1971 - 1972 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Cal-Pac [2 of 2]1971 - 1972 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Revenue Sharing1972 - 1973 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Chronology of Harassment of Huey P. Newton, 1970-19771970-1979 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Petition to Stop the Retrial and Recall Info. 1979 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Committee for Justice for HPN Folder 1 [1 of 3]1968; 1974 - 1980 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Committee for Justice for HPN Folder 1 [2 of 3]1968; 1974 - 1980 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Committee for Justice for HPN Folder 1 [3 of 3]1968; 1974 - 1980 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Justice for Huey Committee (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Committee for Justice1978 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Committee for Justice for HPN Folder 21976 - 1977 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Post July 3, 19771977 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Petition for Probation for H.P.N. 26,000+ names (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Justice for Huey -Thank You Letters1977 - 1978 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Huey P. Newton Misc CRG [re: George Jackson's potential resignation]1977 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - On Eldridge and New York [1 of 2]1969 - 1972 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - On Eldridge and New York [2 of 2]1969 - 1972 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - National Black Political Convention [1 of 2][1972] (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - National Black Political Convention [2 of 2][1972] (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Re: Revolutionary Peoples Constitutional Convention1970 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Rev. Rep. In U.S. & Canada, Western Europe e.g. China, PRG, DRV, Cuba, DKK [1 of 2]1970 - 1971 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Rev. Rep. In U.S. & Canada, Western Europe e.g. China, PRG, DRV, Cuba, DKK [2 of 2]1970 - 1971 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - B.P.P. Delegation's Book Re: People's Republic of China Upon Return (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Puerto Rico (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Notes / Speaking Engagements (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Request for Party Members to Speak (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Speakers' Kit: History of the Black Panther Party1968? (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - General Press Releases1973 - 1974 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Media 1974 - 1976 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Rates Re: Radio Stations and Newspapers1971 - 1973 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - American Documentary Films #21969 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Producer's Funding Corp. "The Mack"1972 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Re: Newton - Channel 131971 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Newsreel - BPP (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Videotapes1971 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Cleaver - Leary Videotapes1971 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - General Info We Have Printed [1 of 3]1972 - 1973 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - General Info We Have Printed [2 of 3]1972 - 1973 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - General Info We Have Printed [3 of 3]1972 - 1973 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Memorial Service for Bobby Hutton1968 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Emory's Printing Service (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - [Black Panther Party Letterhead] (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - [Self-defense buttons - B.P.P] (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - [Misc. Flyers] [1 of 4] (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - [Misc. Flyers] [2 of 4] (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - [Misc. Flyers] [3 of 4] (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - [Misc. Flyers] [4 of 4] (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - The Black Panther News Paper 1977 - 1979 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Information Regarding Our Paper [1 of 8] (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Information Regarding Our Paper [2 of 8] (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Information Regarding Our Paper [3 of 8] (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Information Regarding Our Paper [4 of 8] (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Information Regarding Our Paper [5 of 8] (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Information Regarding Our Paper [6 of 8] (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Information Regarding Our Paper [7 of 8] (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Information Regarding Our Paper [8 of 8] (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - [Samples: Printed by News Web in Chicago - Issue of B.P] (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Greene - B.P.P. Articles - Huggins (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Black Panther Party - Publicity and Miscellaneous [1969] [1 of 4]1969 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Black Panther Party - Publicity and Miscellaneous [1969] [2 of 4]1969 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Black Panther Party - Publicity and Miscellaneous [1969] [3 of 4]1969 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Black Panther Party - Publicity and Miscellaneous [1969] [4 of 4]1969 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - [Organizational Charts] (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Bonds (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Caterers (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Car Rental - Accident Report 1972 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Party Cars1977 - 1980 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - American Air Lines - Claims Filed - 8/11/71 by mail1971 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Claims Filed to Date - United1969 - 1971 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - United Against National Distribution1970 - 1971 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Claims to be Filed - United1969 - 1970 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Power of Attorney Forms (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Passport Application (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - New Contracts (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - [Black Panther Party: Miscellaneous] [1 of 4] (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - [Black Panther Party: Miscellaneous] [2 of 4] (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - [Black Panther Party: Miscellaneous] [3 of 4] (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - [Black Panther Party: Miscellaneous] [4 of 4] (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous - Flyers (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - [Miscellaneous (obituaries, fliers, invitations,etc.)] [1 of 3] (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - [Miscellaneous (obituaries, fliers, invitations,etc.)] [2 of 3] (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - [Miscellaneous (obituaries, fliers, invitations,etc.)] [3 of 3] (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Photos of Seize the Time Bookstore & Miscellaneous Documents (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Subseries 3:Programs, 3
    - Oakland Community School1976 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - OCS Brochure1977 - 1978, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - OCS Fact Sheet (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - OCS Weekly Reports1979 - 1980 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - OCS Graduates, 19771977 - 1980 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Oakland Community School - Graduation 19801979 - 1980 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - OCS Enrollment / Sept. 77- Jan 781977 - 1978 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - OCS Certification Certificate1977 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - CTBS-Nov.1976 [OCS]1977 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - OCS Evacuation Procedures1976 - 1977 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - OCS - Montclarion Article1976 - 1977 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - OCS CTBS - July 19761976 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - [OCS flyers, invitations, etc.] [1 of 2]1978 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - [OCS flyers, invitations, etc.] [2 of 2]1978 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Funding Terms and Conditions for Child Development Program FY 1982-83 [1 of 2] (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Funding Terms and Conditions for Child Development Program FY 1982-83 [2 of 2] (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - [Oakland Community School Instructor Handbook] (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Oakland Community School - Instructor Handbook - Huey P. Newton (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Curriculum Design (1976-1977) [1 of 4] (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Curriculum Design (1976-1977) [2 of 4] (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Curriculum Design (1976-1977) [3 of 4] (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Curriculum Design (1976-1977) [4 of 4] (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - George L. Jackson Clinic (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - B.P.P. Clinic (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Info. On Our Medical Clinics [1 of 2] (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Info. On Our Medical Clinics [2 of 2] (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Health Cadre Report [1 of 2] (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Health Cadre Report [2 of 2] (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Articles on Sickle Cell Anemia and Our Clinics & Health Cadre Reports (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Senior Citizens (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Senior Citizen "Muggings" in Oakland1972 - 1973 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Senior Mini Market1977 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Food Buying Group (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Black Community Survival Conference - March 29 - 31, 19721972 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - May 13th Black Community Survival Conference1972 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Son of Man Temple1973 - 1974 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Ideological Institute Black Panther Party1970 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Subscription Drive1972 - 1973 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - B.P.P.Community Transport Program 1970 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Voter Registration Elections Committee [1 of 4]1971 - 1973 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Voter Registration Elections Committee [2 of 4]1971 - 1973 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Voter Registration Elections Committee [3 of 4]1971 - 1973 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Voter Registration Elections Committee [4 of 4]1971 - 1973 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Anti-War, African Liberation, Voter Registration, Survival Conference June 24, 19721972 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - W.O.P.C. Elections1972 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 4: Stronghold, 4
    - Stronghold Corporation (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Stronghold Corporation (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Stronghold Properties Info. (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Stronghold Properties Info. (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Property Information [1 of 2]1972 - 1977 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Property Information [2 of 2]1972 - 1977 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Property (General) [1 of 2]1970 - 1974 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Property (General) [2 of 2]1970 - 1974 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Properties - Original1977 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Bay Area Properties 1977 (Box 19, Folder 14)